This video highlights how homepages and
Business Central give fast access to
tools we need every day in different
roles while keeping all features close
at hand. We all do different things at
the office depending on our role. In my
settings, we can change our role and
configure the homepage to be most
efficient in our work. The business
manager homepage gathers activities and
information that keep a business running
smoothly. sales and purchase documents,
payments that need attention, and
balances are right up
front. The account and homepage lets us
monitor payments and approvals, view
finance performance charts, and work
with accounts receivable, accounts
payable, bank transactions, and
more. The sales and relationships
homepage helps us control our sales
processes.
We can stay on top of ongoing
opportunities, send sales quotes to
customers and contacts, manage
campaigns, and keep a close eye on sales
in our
pipeline. The project manager homepage
gives us an overview of work in process
on current projects and makes it easy to
stay on budget. We can set up jobs and
plan tasks, manage resources, and
purchase items and
supplies. All homepages have the same
layout. The tiles in the activity
section go to daily tasks like
processing orders or invoices. The
charts offer up-to-date information that
supports decisions. Section headings let
us make light customizations to the
page. For example, we can change the
period that a chart shows information
for or switch to another
chart. What if I want to access other
features? Clicking the menu header will
open all features. And we can even
explore more roles there by expanding
the explore more roles
section. If we are looking for a
particular page, we can always search
for it in the search
bar. Here's a fun tip. Clicking the alt
key on the keyboard will trigger the
shortcut keys. Then we can, for example,
click the J and S keys to open sales and
then again the S key to open sales
quotes.
Now we can work on our sales quotes
quickly. Thank you for watching.